DHARUN NISHANTH S

Application Developer

Passionate and self-motivated programmer curious in learning and working on life changing technologies to solve various problems. Being worked as a developer, I am able to contribute something to the application throughout it's lifecycle. I always love to explore new roles.

Work Experience

Cognizant Chennai, Tamil Nadu 07/2020 - present

Program Analyst

- enabled and customized CI/CD pipelines for projects in
- fix and resolve application vulnerabilities
- migrated 4 applications from brownfield to greenfield.

07/2019 - 07/2020

Program Analyst Trainee

- was part of rewriting a trading application for a banking client.
- developed the decommissioning UI for the application

02/2019 - 03/2019, 05/2019

Full Stack Developer Intern

- Designed the UI and developed 2 functionalities of an Airport Management System web app as part of internship project

Skills

Languages		Frameworks		Tools
Java 8 Bash Script SQL HTML CSS YAML		Hibernate		Eclipse Gitlab CI/CD Maven Jenkins Ansible Veracode

Education

2015-2019

Karpagam Institute of Technology, Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu

- B.E- Electrical & Electronics Engineering
- 7.35 CGPA

Personal Information



Books/Audio Books, Singing, Drawing/Painting



H2, I Floor, TNHB, Rajiv Gandhi Nagar, Sowripalayam (P.O), Coimbatore -641 028



sdharunnishanth@gmail.com



